{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945141379","data":{"timestamp":" 946945141379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" aedc8faf-25ca-41cf-9514-6e2a61e1db93"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945146217","data":{"timestamp":" 946945146217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" aedc8faf-25ca-41cf-9514-6e2a61e1db93"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945149871","data":{"timestamp":" 946945149871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" aedc8faf-25ca-41cf-9514-6e2a61e1db93"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945154846","data":{"timestamp":" 946945154846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" aedc8faf-25ca-41cf-9514-6e2a61e1db93"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945159447","data":{"timestamp":" 946945159447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" aedc8faf-25ca-41cf-9514-6e2a61e1db93"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945166322","data":{"timestamp":" 946945166322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" aedc8faf-25ca-41cf-9514-6e2a61e1db93"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945184124","data":{"timestamp":" 946945184124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 6eaff126-6846-4fe1-b5a0-b17bb24697af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945190635","data":{"timestamp":" 946945190635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 6eaff126-6846-4fe1-b5a0-b17bb24697af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945195110","data":{"timestamp":" 946945195110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 6eaff126-6846-4fe1-b5a0-b17bb24697af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945201282","data":{"timestamp":" 946945201281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 6eaff126-6846-4fe1-b5a0-b17bb24697af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945213376","data":{"timestamp":" 946945213376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 6eaff126-6846-4fe1-b5a0-b17bb24697af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945218668","data":{"timestamp":" 946945218668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 6eaff126-6846-4fe1-b5a0-b17bb24697af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945221022","data":{"timestamp":" 946945221021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 6eaff126-6846-4fe1-b5a0-b17bb24697af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945242629","data":{"timestamp":" 946945242629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945243002","data":{"timestamp":" 946945243002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945243485","data":{"timestamp":" 946945243485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945243828","data":{"timestamp":" 946945243828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945244232","data":{"timestamp":" 946945244232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945244706","data":{"timestamp":" 946945244706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945244930","data":{"timestamp":" 946945244930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945248149","data":{"timestamp":" 946945248148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945248183","data":{"timestamp":" 946945248182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945248897","data":{"timestamp":" 946945248897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945249290","data":{"timestamp":" 946945249290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945249584","data":{"timestamp":" 946945249583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945249787","data":{"timestamp":" 946945249787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945249981","data":{"timestamp":" 946945249981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945250295","data":{"timestamp":" 946945250295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945250519","data":{"timestamp":" 946945250519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945253789","data":{"timestamp":" 946945253789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945254203","data":{"timestamp":" 946945254202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945256716","data":{"timestamp":" 946945256715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945256930","data":{"timestamp":" 946945256929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945257143","data":{"timestamp":" 946945257142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945258626","data":{"timestamp":" 946945258626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945258714","data":{"timestamp":" 946945258714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 7ecdbfcf-e16c-43ab-943c-6319be916029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945273521","data":{"timestamp":" 946945273520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" GUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945276257","data":{"timestamp":" 946945276256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" GUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945277876","data":{"timestamp":" 946945277876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gauni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" GAUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945283389","data":{"timestamp":" 946945283388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gauni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" GAUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945284975","data":{"timestamp":" 946945284975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945287377","data":{"timestamp":" 946945287376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945288967","data":{"timestamp":" 946945288967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" giza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945291346","data":{"timestamp":" 946945291345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" giza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945292949","data":{"timestamp":" 946945292948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945295421","data":{"timestamp":" 946945295421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945297033","data":{"timestamp":" 946945297032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ganda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANDA"," userResponse":" GANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945299535","data":{"timestamp":" 946945299534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ganda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANDA"," userResponse":" GANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945301134","data":{"timestamp":" 946945301133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945303915","data":{"timestamp":" 946945303914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945305541","data":{"timestamp":" 946945305540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945307794","data":{"timestamp":" 946945307793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945309393","data":{"timestamp":" 946945309392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945311795","data":{"timestamp":" 946945311794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945313416","data":{"timestamp":" 946945313416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" GODORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945315937","data":{"timestamp":" 946945315937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" GODORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945317963","data":{"timestamp":" 946945317962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945318039","data":{"timestamp":" 946945318039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 67752a1a-c2ef-48f9-a13a-3005428fc415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" GODORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945331943","data":{"timestamp":" 946945331942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" GUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945345973","data":{"timestamp":" 946945345972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945347588","data":{"timestamp":" 946945347588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gauni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" GAUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945351669","data":{"timestamp":" 946945351669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gauni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" START_GAUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945355146","data":{"timestamp":" 946945355145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gauni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945356743","data":{"timestamp":" 946945356743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945359682","data":{"timestamp":" 946945359681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945361283","data":{"timestamp":" 946945361283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" giza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945364812","data":{"timestamp":" 946945364811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" giza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945366428","data":{"timestamp":" 946945366427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945368732","data":{"timestamp":" 946945368731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945370329","data":{"timestamp":" 946945370328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ganda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANDA"," userResponse":" GANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945373663","data":{"timestamp":" 946945373662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ganda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANDA"," userResponse":" GANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945375280","data":{"timestamp":" 946945375279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945378315","data":{"timestamp":" 946945378315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945379925","data":{"timestamp":" 946945379925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945382263","data":{"timestamp":" 946945382262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945383873","data":{"timestamp":" 946945383872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945386227","data":{"timestamp":" 946945386226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOTI"," userResponse":" GOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945387823","data":{"timestamp":" 946945387822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" GODORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945390323","data":{"timestamp":" 946945390322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" GODORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945392341","data":{"timestamp":" 946945392340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945392414","data":{"timestamp":" 946945392413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" a063972c-a81b-4069-b0c9-0a0f4cc9d63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" godoro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GODORO"," userResponse":" GODORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945417334","data":{"timestamp":" 946945417334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_p-g-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945422266","data":{"timestamp":" 946945422265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_w-g-v"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945426940","data":{"timestamp":" 946945426940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-m-h"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945430756","data":{"timestamp":" 946945430756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_l-z-g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945434250","data":{"timestamp":" 946945434249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_i-g-n"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945438602","data":{"timestamp":" 946945438602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_t-r-g"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945442367","data":{"timestamp":" 946945442367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_h-v-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945445885","data":{"timestamp":" 946945445885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_b-m-g"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945449513","data":{"timestamp":" 946945449513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_t-k-g"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945453159","data":{"timestamp":" 946945453159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_w-g-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945454937","data":{"timestamp":" 946945454936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 27883abe-0a41-4eee-9449-fb8d6d2baabd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_g_w-g-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945474419","data":{"timestamp":" 946945474419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3848d34f-d768-4b55-8802-b8620ec252c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945523774","data":{"timestamp":" 946945523773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3848d34f-d768-4b55-8802-b8620ec252c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945523916","data":{"timestamp":" 946945523915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3848d34f-d768-4b55-8802-b8620ec252c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945549780","data":{"timestamp":" 946945549780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-g-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945554829","data":{"timestamp":" 946945554829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_ch-g-h"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945558704","data":{"timestamp":" 946945558703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-h-j"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945562042","data":{"timestamp":" 946945562042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-g-a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945565201","data":{"timestamp":" 946945565201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-b-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945569757","data":{"timestamp":" 946945569756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_v-e-g"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945574908","data":{"timestamp":" 946945574907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_v-e-g"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945580784","data":{"timestamp":" 946945580784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-e-p"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945586134","data":{"timestamp":" 946945586134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_w-v-g"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945591762","data":{"timestamp":" 946945591761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_w-v-g"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945594967","data":{"timestamp":" 946945594967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-i-t"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945598711","data":{"timestamp":" 946945598711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_j-m-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945603697","data":{"timestamp":" 946945603697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" fc60ff5d-7dfe-4144-8f60-d5e1ff9fa7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.91"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_g_j-m-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945634079","data":{"timestamp":" 946945634079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_g_w"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945640715","data":{"timestamp":" 946945640715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_g_m"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945647355","data":{"timestamp":" 946945647355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_k_j_g"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945653974","data":{"timestamp":" 946945653974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_h_g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945660625","data":{"timestamp":" 946945660624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_g_s_w"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945667241","data":{"timestamp":" 946945667240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_z_g"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945673897","data":{"timestamp":" 946945673897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_a_g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945680520","data":{"timestamp":" 946945680520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_g_a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945687175","data":{"timestamp":" 946945687175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_g_d_u"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945693812","data":{"timestamp":" 946945693812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_g_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945701284","data":{"timestamp":" 946945701284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_g_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945713334","data":{"timestamp":" 946945713334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_d_g_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945731654","data":{"timestamp":" 946945731653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_d_g_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945753428","data":{"timestamp":" 946945753428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 3637a6f4-e27b-4afa-b638-818245b276ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_d_g_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945783137","data":{"timestamp":" 946945783136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 6ef32f24-5994-4645-8eba-010aebb0aee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945788128","data":{"timestamp":" 946945788127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 6ef32f24-5994-4645-8eba-010aebb0aee5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945812285","data":{"timestamp":" 946945812285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945813327","data":{"timestamp":" 946945813327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945819088","data":{"timestamp":" 946945819087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945820159","data":{"timestamp":" 946945820159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945823127","data":{"timestamp":" 946945823127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945824205","data":{"timestamp":" 946945824204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945827396","data":{"timestamp":" 946945827395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945828453","data":{"timestamp":" 946945828453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945831148","data":{"timestamp":" 946945831148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945832188","data":{"timestamp":" 946945832188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945833581","data":{"timestamp":" 946945833581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945833660","data":{"timestamp":" 946945833660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_031844"," gameId":" 98b2fa8d-f642-42c9-b9fb-318bb0f2f140"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}